<Document>
  # Space Stories - Marine Corps Game Rules

  The rules in this section and the in-game guide are primary and take priority over all other sources, including Discord and the Wiki.

  ## Recent Changes 04.09.2026
  - [textlink="Rule 10: Military Law and Mutinies" link="STENGMilitaryLawMutinies"] fixed the text regarding evacuation mutinies.

  ## Recent Changes 04.05.2026
  - [textlink="Rule 2: Role-Playing" link="STENGRolePlay"] and [textlink="Rule 7: Play Your Role" link="STENGPlayYourRole"] have been updated: detailed requirements for portraying different types of survivors have been added.
  - [textlink="RU (Non-Modifiable Third-Party Provisions)" link="STMarineSOPNONModThirdparty"] has been completely revised.

  ## Administrative decisions are final.
  - Rules are applied according to their intent. It is impossible to list every violation example; therefore enforcement depends on administrative interpretation of the rule’s meaning.
  - Administrators may resolve rule violations using in-game consequences for characters at their discretion. This does not apply to zero-tolerance rules.
  - You may submit an appeal to head staff if you believe a decision was incorrect.

  ## General Information
  Disabling, ignoring, or refusing to answer an admin’s ahelp will result in a ban that is only appealable.
  This is to prevent players from avoiding consequences. If you need to leave urgently, inform us — this will be taken into account when reviewing an appeal.

  All rules below apply at all times, including between rounds.

  ## Core Rules
  These are the primary Space Stories - Marine Corps rules. Click on them for detailed information.
  - [textlink="Rule 0: Community Expectations" link="STENGCommunityExpectations"]
  - [textlink="Rule 1: Grief" link="STENGGrief"]
  - [textlink="Rule 2: Roleplay" link="STENGRolePlay"]
  - [textlink="Rule 3: Metagaming and Metacommunication" link="STENGMetagamingMetacommunication"]
  - [textlink="Rule 4: ERP" link="STENGERP"]
  - [textlink="Rule 5: Bug Abuse and Unfair Play" link="STENGBuggingFoulPlay"]
  - [textlink="Rule 6: Ban Evasion and Multi-Accounts" link="STENGBypassBlockingMultiAccounts"]
  - [textlink="Rule 7: Play Your Role" link="STENGPlayYourRole"]
  - [textlink="Rule 8: Character Names" link="STENGCharacterNames"]
  - [textlink="Rule 9: Use of Lethal Force" link="STENGUseOfLethalForce"]
  - [textlink="Rule 10: Military Law and Mutinies" link="STENGMilitaryLawMutinies"]
</Document>
